The caterer sent me this list of 12 appetizers. I have to narrow it to 6.
外燴的公司給我十二道開胃菜清單 我得將選擇範圍縮小到六項
Food? Oh, give me.
食物問題？交給我吧
Did Monica mention we're trying to get The Swing Kings to play the wedding?
摩妮卡跟你們提過我們結婚時 要請搖擺國王來演唱嗎？
You're into swing music?
你喜歡搖擺音樂？
I used to go all over town listening to bands.
我以前會跑遍全城聽樂團演奏
-Chandler? -Gap commercial.
-錢德？ -在GAP的廣告看到的
-Did you book them? Did you call? -I will.
-你打電話訂下他們了嗎？ -我會打的
-You want me to call? -I'll do it. You stick to your job.
-你要我打嗎？ -我會打的，你只需要做好你的工作
-What is your job? -Staying out of the way.
-你的工作是什麼？ -別礙事
This is impossible. Why don't you just pick all 15?
這是不可能的，你為什麼不挑清單上的十五道開胃菜？
-There were only 12. -Oh, yeah, I added 3.
-只有十二道而已 -對，我加了三道
What are "peanut-butter fingers"?
什麼是花生醬手指？
The One With the Cheap Wedding Dress
本集播出：廉價的婚紗
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Well, hello.
你好
She's cute.
她好可愛
Should we go talk to her?
我們該跟她說話嗎？
Sure. Being engaged, I'm not nervous to talk to pretty girls anymore.
當然，訂婚後跟美女說話 我再也不會緊張
Could you guys help me?
你們能過來幫幫我嗎？
Yeah, let me get that for you.
我來幫你搬那個
-It's really heavy. -I got it.
-它真的很重 -沒問題
So hi, I'm Ross, and this is my friend, Chandler.
嗨，我是羅斯，他是我朋友錢德
I'm Kristen.
我是克麗絲汀
Hi. Are you new to the area?
克麗絲汀，嗨，你剛搬來嗎？
I'd love to show you around sometime.
如果你剛搬來這裡 我可以帶你四處參觀一下
I actually just moved from four blocks over.
事實上，我從四條街外搬來這裡
But this block is like another world.
但這裡好像另一個世界
Actually, it does have a very interesting history.
事實上這個地區的歷史非常有趣
This street is the first in the city to have an underground sewer system.
這條街是紐約 第一條有下水道系統的街道
Before that, sewage and waste...
之前污水跟廢棄物…
would just flow right down the street.
會直接流到街上
Sometimes ankle-deep.
有時深及腳踝
Smooth.
說的好
Excuse me?
你說什麼？
You're gonna be starving after moving. What do you say I take you to dinner?
搬完家後你一定會肚子餓 你想跟我一起去吃晚餐嗎？
-I'd like that. -Great.
-我很樂意 -太棒了
Let me take this up.
我幫你把箱子搬上去
-After you. -Oh, no. After you.
-你先請 -不，你先請
Oh, my God!
我的天啊！
Am I crazy, or does this totally go?
是我瘋了還是這真的很配？
Oh, my God! You look so beautiful!
我的天啊！你看起來好漂亮！
Thank you, Rachel. But look at Monica!
謝謝你，瑞秋，但看看摩妮卡！
This is it. Yeah, this is the one.
就是它，就是這件
I can't believe I found it.
我不敢相信我找到它了
Wow, you look so beautiful. If I knew you, I'd cry.
你看起來好漂亮 如果我認識你，我會哭的
I'm Monica Geller. Bawl like a baby.
我是摩妮卡蓋勒，幸福的新娘
I'm Megan Bailey.
我是梅根巴利
-Have you found your dress? -These dresses are amazing...
-你找到婚紗了嗎？ -這些婚紗都很漂亮…
-but I couldn't afford one. -I can't either.
-但我買不起 -我也是
I'm here to figure out the one I want,  then I'll get it at Kleinman's.
我只是來這裡找婚紗 然後我會到克萊門婚紗店買
They're having a huge sale.
他們在大減價
-Thanks for the tip. -When are you getting married?
-謝謝你的情報 -你什麼時候結婚？
-I'm not. I just like to try them on. -I do the same thing.
-我沒有要結婚，我只是想試穿婚紗 -我也會那麼做
I'm just kidding. I'm getting married July 25th.
我只是在開玩笑 我的婚期是七月二十五日
I'm just kidding too.
我也只是在開玩笑
I'm getting married in December.
我要在十二月結婚
-When are you getting married? -May 15th.
-你什麼時候結婚？ -五月十五日
It's close. Who's your photographer?
已經很接近了，你請誰拍照？
-Jeffrey. -We met with him.
-傑佛瑞 -我們跟他談過
-Did he show you nude wedding photos? -The Best Man? Wow!
-他拿裸體婚紗照給你們看了嗎？ -那個伴郎嗎？哇！
I know. I almost called off my wedding.
我知道，我差點取消了婚禮
-Who's your band? -My fiance wants The Swing Kings.
-你請了哪個樂團？ -我未婚夫想請搖擺國王
You're lucky. My fiance wants the heavy metal band, Carcass.
你真幸運，我未婚夫想請屍體 那重金屬樂團
Is that spelled with a "C" or a "K"? It doesn't matter, they're both great!
是濕體還是屍體？ 那不重要，他們都很棒！
Oh, don't buy that here.
別在這裡買婚紗
Now that you know what you want,  go to Kleinman's.
現在你知道你喜歡哪一件 到克萊門婚紗店買
This place is so overpriced.
這裡的婚紗太貴了
I own this store.
我是這裡的老闆
So does this come in another color, or...
這件婚紗有別的顏色嗎？還是…？
Hi. You moving in or moving out?
嗨，你要搬進來還是搬走？
-Moving in. -Can I help out?
-我要搬進來 -需要我幫忙嗎？
Okay, but be careful. The guy who was helping before hurt his back.
好吧，但是你得小心一點 來幫我的那個人因為背痛先走了
-Boyfriend? -No.
-他是你男朋友？ -不是
I'm Joey.
我是喬伊
Kristen.
我是克麗絲汀
What a beautiful name.
你的名字真好聽
What is it again?
你說你叫什麼來著？
Kristen.
克麗絲汀
-You live around here? -Right down there.
-你住在附近？ -我就住在那邊
Let me give you a tip.
我得提供你一些資訊
Don't take a nap on this stoop. You could wake up without shoes.
別在那個樓梯上睡覺 醒過來時你的鞋子可能已經被偷了
I'll remember that.
我會記住的
Listen, would you like to have dinner with me tonight?
聽著，今晚你要跟我一起吃飯嗎？
I have plans tonight. How about tomorrow?
今晚我有約了，明天可以嗎？
Sounds great. Well, where does this go?
聽起來不錯，這個要搬到哪裡？
You look strong. Why don't you grab one of the boxes.
你看起來很壯，把它交給我 你去幫我搬箱子吧
（書，枕頭）
Yeah, I'll get this one.
對，我要挑這一個
（克萊門婚紗店五折大減價）
So this is Brooklyn?
這裡就是布魯克林？
Listen up. There's only one dress in each size.
聽著，通常每件婚紗 一個尺寸只有一件
So when they open those doors,  fan out.
他們一開門，馬上衝進去
This is what you're looking for. Memorize it.
這就是你們的目標，記住它
When you locate the dress,  blow on these, all right?
找到婚紗後就吹哨子，好嗎？
Three sharp blasts. When you hear it, come running.
用力吹三聲，一聽到哨音後 馬上跑過來
Here he comes!
他來了！
-They're pushing! -Don't be a baby!
-她們在推我！ -別那麼孩子氣！
-Out of the way! -Let's go!
-別擋路！ -我們沖吧！
Rachel?! Come on!
瑞秋？！快一點！
No, not it. Not it. Not it.
不，不是
Don't crowd me.
別推我
This is it! This is the dress! It's perfect!
就是它！就是這件婚紗！太完美了！
I'm sorry, this one's taken!
對不起，這件是我的！
-Megan! -Monica!
-梅根！ -摩妮卡！
-You came! -Yeah!
-你來了！ -對！
-This is my dress! -No!
-這是我的婚紗！ -不！
-You saw me wearing it. -And now you'll see me buying it.
-你看到我試穿它 -現在你會看到我買下它
You freak!
你這個怪胎！
You wouldn't even know about this place without me.
如果沒有我你根本不知道這個地方
-Look, you don't want to fight me. -Maybe I do. I'm pretty feisty!
-聽著，你不會想跟我爭 -或許我想，我是很凶的！
-I'm coming! I'm coming! -Hey!
-我來了… -嘿！
Okay! Hey? Oh, what do I do?!
好了！嘿？我該怎麼辦？！
What are you doing? Did you find the dress?
你在做什麼？你找到婚紗了嗎？
Did you find the dress?
你找到婚紗了嗎？
No. You gotta get me out of here.
不，快救我出去，這些女人都瘋了
-We've gotta get Monica. -You hold my hand!
-我們得去找摩妮卡 -你得抓住我的手！
Excuse me! Excuse me!
對不起…
Go! Go! Go!
快走…
（中央公園咖啡廳）
How was your date the other night?
羅斯，那天你跟她約會還順利吧？
Did you tell her about the magical ride that starts with every flush?
你跟她提過只要一按馬桶 魔法之旅就開始了嗎？
Laugh all you want, but she said she'd like to go out again.
儘管笑吧，但她說她想再跟我約會
In fact, I'll go call her right now.
事實上，我正要打電話給她
And I'll make sure and tell her my friend Chandler says...
我會確定並告訴她我朋友錢德說…
Sorry I didn't stop by last night, but I had a date.
抱歉昨晚我失約了，但我有個約會
When it's 1:00 in the morning and you don't come by, that's okay.
你說你凌晨一點要過來 就算你放我鴿子也沒有關係
It was with this really hot girl who moved in across the street.
我跟一個辣妹約會，她剛剛搬到對街
-Right across the street? -Yeah.
-真的嗎？她住在對街？ -對
-When did you meet her? -Two days ago.
-你什麼時候認識她的？ -兩天前
Excellent!
太棒了！
You know, Ross met somebody too.
羅斯也認識了一個女孩
-Hey. -How'd it go?
-嘿 -怎麼樣？
We're going out again Saturday.
太棒了，我們星期六要再出去玩
But I found out she's also seeing some other guy.
但我剛剛發現她也在跟別人約會
Really?
真的嗎？
Joe, what would you do if you were in Ross' situation?
喬伊，如果你是羅斯你會怎麼做？
I am. I'm dating this girl who's also seeing another guy.
我跟他差不多 跟我約會的女孩也在跟別人約會
But I'm not worried about it.
但我一點都不擔心
You shouldn't be. I wouldn't want to be the guy who's up against you.
你不必擔心，我不想當你的競爭者
I mean, that doofus is going to lose.
那個混蛋一定會輸的
So this is nice.
這真的太有趣了
I wish I didn't have to go. Believe me.
真希望我能留下來，相信我
But I have to.
但我得走了
So, what's the name of the girl you're dating?
對了，跟你們約會的女孩 叫什麼名字？
-Kristen Leigh. -Bye.
-克麗絲汀萊夫 -再見
Well, only one of us can keep dating her.
很明顯地，我們之中 只有一個人能繼續跟她約會
Obviously. So how do we decide?
沒錯，我們該怎麼決定？
Well, now,  let's look at this objectively.
好了，我們得客觀地來解決這件事
I think I should date her.
我想我該跟她約會
Or I'm the one who dates her.
或是我該跟她約會
That's interesting. But check this out. I date her.
那真的很有趣 但是聽好了，我跟她約會
Okay, but to go in another direction..
好吧，但是換個角度來說…
Okay. This can go on for a while.
好吧，我們是談不出結論來的
-We should order some food then. -No, Joey.
-那麼我們該點些吃的 -不，喬伊
Look, why don't we just let her decide, okay?
聽著，我們為什麼不讓她來決定呢？
We'll each go out with her one more time.
我們都再跟她約會一次
And we'll see who she likes best.
看看她比較喜歡誰
That sounds fair.
聽起來很公平
Maybe I'll take her to that new French restaurant.
或許我會帶她 到新開的法國餐廳吃飯
Wait a second. We have to set a spending limit.
等一下，我們得對約會費用設下限制
I can't take her to a fancy place like that.
我沒有錢帶她到高級餐廳吃飯
Well, sorry. That's what I do on dates.
抱歉，那是我的約會方式
Well, I guess I'll just have to do what I do on dates.
我猜我得用我的約會方式
-So let's decide on a spending limit. -Yeah.
-我們來決定費用上限 -好吧
And a slice...
大概是…
six dollars?
六塊錢？
-I was thinking more like 100. -Okay.
-我想是一百塊 -好吧
Can I borrow 94 dollars?
你能借我九十四塊嗎？
I know. Can you hand me a tissue?
我知道，你能幫我拿張面紙嗎？
You're out of Diet Coke.
你家沒有健怡可樂了
Hello?
喂？
What? You what?
什麼？你什麼？
You listen here, missy!
你給我聽好了，小姐！
Megan booked The Swing Kings on the day of our wedding...
是梅根打來的，她訂下搖擺國王 日期是我們結婚的那一天…
and said she'd only give them back for the dress!
還說如果我不把婚紗讓給她 我就沒有樂團
Does that mean Carcass is available?
那麼說的話屍體有空了？
What am I gonna do? That's the dress! That is "the" dress!
我該怎麼辦？我好喜歡那件婚紗！
Chandler wants the band. What do I do?
錢德喜歡那個樂團，我該怎麼辦？
-Figure out how to talk him out of it. -How?
-想辦法說服他放棄 -怎麼說服？
You're out of toilet paper!
你家的衛生紙用完了！
I wanted to wish you good luck on your date.
我要來祝你約會順利
-Thanks. -What time are you meeting?
-謝謝 -你們約幾點？
We have reservations at Grand Merci Bistro at 8.
我們在葛蘭梅西畢斯多餐廳 訂了八點的位子
That's in 20 minutes. You'd better get dressed.
時間只剩二十分鐘 你最好快去換衣服
-I am dressed. -Oh, well, good.
-我已經換好衣服了 -太好了
For me.
對我來說
What's this? Did you give yourself a facial?
這是什麼？你在敷臉？
I have an oily T-zone.
我的T字部位很會出油
Okay, dude.
好吧，兄弟
-You sent Kristen flowers? -That's right.
-你送克麗絲汀花？ -沒錯
You spent 100 dollars. That's the limit. You're screwed!
你花了一百塊 你把錢花光了，你輸了！
I sent the flowers before the actual date, so technically...
我在約會前送她花 所以技術上來說…
I didn't break any rules.
我沒有犯規
Thanks for stopping by though.
謝謝你來看我
That's how it's gonna be? I can break the rules too.
你真的要那麼玩？我也可以犯規
-What are you gonna do? -I don't know.
-你打算怎麼辦？ -我不知道
-I'm not surprised. -You won't get away with this.
-為什麼我一點都不訝異？ -我不會放過你的
-You don't have much choice. -We'll see!
-我想你沒有太多選擇 -我們走著瞧
Hey! So, just a light layer?
嘿！只要薄薄地敷一層就好？
Yeah, just here and there.
對，只要敷這裡跟這裡
Joey got meat sauce on the banister again.
喬伊又把肉醬滴在欄杆上了
Swing music is so out.
搖擺音樂太落伍了
He's gotta be in the room for that to work.
他得在這房間裡才可以聽的到
What are you guys talking about?
你們到底在說什麼？
We're talking about The Swing Kings...
我們在談搖擺國王…
and whether they're the right way to go.
討論到底該不該請他們來
I went to a wedding where they had swing music...
有一次我去參加 請搖擺樂團來表演的婚禮…
two months later the couple divorced.
兩個月後他們就離婚了
I'm not saying there's any connection here...
我不是說這其中有什麼關係…
but they did say that's why they got divorced.
但他們的確告訴我 那是他們離婚的原因
But I love swing music!
但我喜歡搖擺音樂！
But The Swing Kings?
但搖擺國王？
They suck so much that people die at their concerts. They stop living.
他們爛到有人聽他們的演唱會死掉 他們就是不想活了
When Monica and I went to see them,  we had fun.
我只知道摩妮卡跟我 去看他們演唱時非常開心
And there's another reason.
事實上還有一個原因
-Well, what is the other reason? -I don't want to say.
-是什麼原因？ -我不想說
Well, you have to,  because maybe it's stupid.
你非說不可，或許它很愚蠢
It's just, while Monica and I were dancing to them...
摩妮卡跟我隨著他們的音樂起舞…
it was the first time I knew that...
我第一次知道…
you were the woman that I wanted to dance all my dances with.
你就是我想一輩子共舞的女人
Oh, crap.
喔，爛透了
-Our table will be ready soon. -Oh, great.
-我們的桌子馬上就會準備好 -太棒了
-Is your back feeling better? -That's fine.
-你的背好一點了嗎？ -沒事了
I guess the more muscles you have...
我猜肌肉越多…
the more they can spasm out of control.
就越可能抽筋
-Kristen? -Joey!
-克麗絲汀？ -喬伊！
-What are you doing here? -I like this place.
-你來這裡做什麼？ -我喜歡這個地方
And technically, I'm not breaking any rules, so...
技術上來說，我沒有犯規，所以…
Well, Ross, this is Joey. Joey, Ross.
羅斯，他是喬伊 喬伊，羅斯
-Hi. -Hi. It's nice to meet you.
-嗨 -嗨，很高興能認識你
I used to have a friend named Joey.
我以前有個朋友叫喬伊
I don't anymore.
但他不再是我朋友
Our table will be ready in a couple minutes.
我們的桌子馬上就會準備好
Sure! I would love to wait with you guys! Thanks!
當然，我想跟你們一起等！謝謝！
So, Joey, you look familiar.
喬伊，你看起來好眼熟
Are you on TV or something?
你上過電視嗎？
He doesn't like to talk about it...
喬伊不喜歡提這件事…
but he's one of the stars of Days of Our Lives.
但他主演過《我們的日子》
That's right. Don't you play a woman?
沒錯，你不是演女人嗎？
A woman in a man's body.
那是被困在男人身體裡的女人
Much better.
那可好多了
It's funny, because you look familiar to me too.
真有趣，因為我也覺得你很眼熟
Have you ever been married?
你結過婚嗎？
Yes, I have.
我結過婚
In fact, just the other day...
事實上，前幾天…
Kris and I talked about how I've been married and have a son.
克麗絲跟我還談到 我結過婚，有個兒子
-Little Eric. -That's right. Wait. No, Ben.
-小艾力克 -沒錯，等一下，不，是班才對
So you've just been married the one time then?
你只結過一次婚嗎？
-Well... -You've been married twice?
-嗯… -你結過兩次婚？
Yes. And...
對，那個…
another time after that.
之後又結了一次
Boy, I'm getting hungry.
天啊，我餓了
Have you ever been so hungry on a date...
你曾經在約會時餓到…
that when the girl goes to the bathroom, you eat her food?
趁女伴去上洗手間 偷吃掉她的食物嗎？
You said the waiter ate my crab cake.
你說服務生吃掉我的蟹餅
So, Ross, now why did that first marriage break up?
羅斯，你的第一段婚姻為什麼會結束？
Was it because the woman was straight or because she was a lesbian?
因為你前妻是異性戀 或因為她是同性戀？
-Do you two know each other? -No.
-你們認識嗎？ -不認識
But he seems like a guy who'd marry a woman...
只是羅斯看起來像是 會跟有同性戀傾向的女人…
on the verge of being a lesbian and then push her over the edge.
結婚後，逼得她非得出櫃的男人
Wait a minute! Were you on a poster for gonorrhea?
等一下，你拍過淋病海報吧？
Have you ever slept in the same bed with a monkey?
你跟猴子同床共枕過吧？
You leave Marcel out of this!
別把馬賽扯進來！
Fine! You ever gotten stuck in a pair of leather pants?
好吧，你曾經被自己的皮褲卡住了？
Have you ever locked yourself in a TV cabinet, VD-boy?
你曾經把自己鎖在電視櫃裡嗎？電視小子
Monkey-lover!
猴子迷！
Where do you think we lost her?
你覺得她是什麼時候離開的？
Probably around gonorrhea.
可能是淋病那一段吧
-Hi, honey, I'm home! -Don't come in here!
-甜心，我回來了！ -別進來！
Why, do you have another boyfriend in there?
怎麼了？你的另一個男朋友在裡面？
No. We only mess around at his place.
不，我們只會在他家胡搞
I started it, but now it's scaring me,  so could you come out here?
雖然是我開的頭 但我開始擔心了，你能出來嗎？
I'm wearing a wedding dress.
不行，我正穿著婚紗
You got a wedding dress?
你買到婚紗了？
-Yeah, but I'm not keeping it. -Then why can't I see it?
-對，但我要把它退回去 -那麼我為什麼不能看到它？
Oh. I guess you can.
我猜應該可以
But I have to return it, so you can't like it.
但我得把它退回去 所以你絕不能喜歡它
Okay, I promise. I'll hate it.
好吧，我發誓我會恨它
Wow. You look hideous.
哇，你看起來好可怕
Really?
真的嗎？
Yeah. That's like the most ugliest dress I've ever seen.
對，那是我看過最醜的婚紗
Why do you have to return it?
你為什麼要把它退回去？
Because it doesn't really fit.
因為它真的不合適
Oh, I booked The Swing Kings.
還有，我訂了搖擺國王
Oh, that's great. Thanks.
那真的是太棒了，謝謝
But that dress is terrible.
但那件婚紗可怕極了
-It makes me want to rip it off you. -Okay.
-它讓我想把它從你身上扯下來 -好吧
But you can't rip it.
但你不可以把它弄破
Well, maybe a little.
或許弄破一點也沒關係
Guys, you want to look at the song list for the wedding?
你們想看看婚禮上 演唱歌曲的清單嗎？
Guys?
怎麼了？
I thought you'd be gone all day.
我還以為你會去一整天
All right, what's going on?
好吧，發生了什麼事？
I'm sorry. I should probably leave you girls alone.
對不起，或許我應該 讓你們這些小女生獨處一下
Laugh all you want, but in 10 minutes we'll have younger-looking skin.
儘管笑吧，但十分鐘後 我們的皮夫會變得又白又嫩
You know, she could use a little...
她該敷一下臉的…
Oh, nice shot! Yeah!
好球！太帥了！